<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TMC Course Finder</string>

    <string name="navigation_course">Courses</string>
    <string name="navigation_favorite">Favorites</string>
    <string name="navigation_about">About us</string>
    <string name="navigation_contact">Contact us</string>

    <string name="toolbar_main_course">TMC Course Finder</string>
    <string name="toolbar_main_favorite">Favorite Courses</string>
    <string name="toolbar_main_about">About us</string>
    <string name="toolbar_main_contact">Contact us</string>

    <string name="toolbar_favorite">Saved favorite courses</string>

    <string name="toolbar_course_discipline">Course by Discipline</string>
    <string name="toolbar_course_institution">Course by Institution</string>

    <string name="toolbar_course_detail">About the course</string>

    <string name="contact_hint_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="contact_hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="contact_hint_mobile">Mobile</string>
    <string name="contact_hint_inquiry">Your inquiry ?</string>
    <string name="contact_button">Mail to TMC</string>

    <string name="about_image_description">About TMC campus</string>
    <string name="course_image_description">Old TMC campus</string>

    <string name="about_link_history">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/about-us/our-history/</string>
    <string name="about_link_welcome">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/about-us/welcome-message/</string>
    <string name="about_link_vision">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/about-us/vision-mission-and-brand/</string>
    <string name="about_link_why">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/about-us/why-tmc-academy/</string>
    <string name="about_link_more">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/about-us/</string>

    <string name="about_button_history">Our History</string>
    <string name="about_button_welcome">Welcome Message</string>
    <string name="about_button_vision">Vision, Mission and Brand</string>
    <string name="about_button_why">Why choose TMC \?</string>
    <string name="about_button_more">More...</string>

    <string name="favorite_saved_course">Saved courses</string>

    <string name="course_label">SEARCH COURSES BY:</string>
    <string name="course_button_discipline">Discipline</string>
    <string name="course_button_institution">Institution</string>

    <string name="course_detail_button">Further detail</string>

    <string name="course_discipline_accounting">Accounting &amp; Finance</string>
    <string name="course_discipline_business">Business</string>
    <string name="course_discipline_hospitality">Hospitality &amp; Tourism</string>
    <string name="course_discipline_infocomm">Infocomm Technology</string>
    <string name="course_discipline_mass_comm">Mass Communication</string>
    <string name="course_discipline_psychology">Psychology</string>

    <string name="course_institution_tmc">TMC Academy</string>
    <string name="course_institution_northampton">University of Northampton - UK</string>
    <string name="course_institution_gloucestershire">University of Gloucestershire - UK</string>
    <string name="course_institution_greenwich">University of Greenwich - UK</string>

    <string name="course_name0">Diploma in Accounting and Finance</string>
    <string name="course_name1">Bachelor of Science (Honours) in Accounting and Finance</string>
    <string name="course_name2">Bachelor of Science (Honours) \n International Accounting (Top Up)</string>
    <string name="course_name3">Post-Graduate Diploma in Accounting \n – A Preparatory Course for UMKC Master of Science in Accounting (MSA)</string>
    <string name="course_name4">Post-Graduate Diploma in Finance \n – A Preparatory Course for UMKC Master of Science in Finance (MSF)</string>
    <string name="course_name5">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) in Accounting and Financial Management Studies (Top-up)</string>
    <string name="course_name6">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) \n Business and Management (Top-Up)</string>
    <string name="course_name7">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) \n Marketing Management (Top-Up)</string>
    <string name="course_name8">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) in \n Business Management and Strategy (Top-up)</string>
    <string name="course_name9">Bachelor of Arts (Honours) \n International Tourism Management (Top Up)</string>
    <string name="course_name10">Higher Diploma in Hospitality and Tourism Management</string>
    <string name="course_name11">Higher Diploma in Tourism, Hospitality and Leisure Management</string>
    <string name="course_name12">International Diploma in Hospitality</string>
    <string name="course_name13">Bachelor of Science (Honours) Computing (Top-up)</string>
    <string name="course_name14">Higher Diploma in Infocomm Technology</string>
    <string name="course_name15">International Diploma in Information Technology</string>
    <string name="course_name16">Higher Diploma in Mass Communication</string>
    <string name="course_name17">International Diploma in Mass Communication</string>
    <string name="course_name18">Bachelor of Science (Honours) \n Psychology with Counselling (Top-up)</string>
    <string name="course_name19">Bachelor of Science (Honours) Psychology (Top-Up)</string>
    <string name="course_name20">Graduate Diploma of Psychology</string>
    <string name="course_name21">Higher Diploma in Psychology with Counselling</string>

    <string name="course_detail0">
        The main aim is to provide the students with the necessary theoretical knowledge
        and the practical aspects to meet career opportunities in the accounting and financial sectors of the economy.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail1">
        This accounting and finance degree is your step into the vast industry.

        \n\n Accountants and finance specialists have a central role in all types of organisations;
        public and private sector, within industry and commerce.
        The accountant has become a key player in the provision of management information to enable successful decision making,
        planning and control. Accounting is more than just a computational skill and the programme will
        develop your ability to analyse and to evaluate real life situations and effectively communicate your views and opinions.
        You will consider practical techniques involved in accounting and finance,
        and develop skills to critically analyse the theory behind these techniques.

        \n\n The Accounting and Finance Division is one of only six universities to have courses accredited by AAT
        (Association of Accounting Technicians). This means that once you graduate you will be able to apply for AAT membership,
        providing you with a professional qualification to enhance your employability.

        \n\n The Division has also retained its accreditations from ACCA
        (Association of Chartered Certified Accountants – 8 exemptions), CIMA (Chartered Institute of Management Accountants),
        ICAEW (Institute of Chartered Accountants in England and Wales) and AIA (Association of International Accountants).
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail2">
        &lt;Awarded by The University of Northampton&gt;

        \n\n The accounting degree awarded by The University of Northampton provides the learners the knowledge within
        which a financial services institution or finance function operates and the financial boundaries to
        which any business operates. In addition the learner will develop a sound critical understanding of the academic foundations,
        which underpin key aspects of accounting and financial management.
        It provides a framework for developing accounting as well as business skills and knowledge needed at all management levels.
        This course is designed for students seeking careers in accounting and financial industry.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail3">
        This programme is designed for students with little or no undergraduate accounting coursework.
        It provides comprehensive coverage of accounting topics necessary for a professional career in the field.
        Completion of the programme also qualifies students for the various examinations leading to professional certification.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail4">
        The Post-Graduate Diploma in Finance (PGDF) is for students and executives seeking specialized training
        in finance in preparation for Master of Science in Finance at University of Missouri –
        Kansas City and the financial certifications such as the Chartered Financial Analyst (CFA),
        and Certified Financial Planner (CFP).
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail5">
        &lt;Awarded by University of Gloucestershire&gt;

        \n\n This degree offers graduates the opportunity to either fast-track their professional accountancy qualification
        or to embark on a career in business. The programme gives graduates a firm foundation for a career in accounting/finance,
        which enables them to make an immediate and effective contribution to the organisation for which they work.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail6">
        &lt;Awarded by The University of Northampton&gt;

        \n\n The business degree awarded by The University of Northampton covers key aspects of business and management practice
        and theory and emphasizes the development of individual and group skills.
        Students can follow a range of pathways to meet their individual interests and career aspirations including marketing,
        finance, human resources and general business.This course is designed for students seeking careers in
        marketing and business industries.

        \n\n Course aims to:

        \n\t &#8226; Become increasingly independent in their learning style, thereby enhancing their life-long learning skills.
        \n\t &#8226; Gain a deep understanding of organisations,their management and the changing external environment
        \n\t &#8226; Be able to contribute effectively in a range of operational and/or strategic contexts in business on completion of the programme and to target careers in one specialist area
        \n\t &#8226; Develop both the knowledge and the ability to use a range of research techniques.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail7">
        &lt;Awarded by The University of Northampton&gt;

        \n\n The degree awarded by The University of Northampton offers graduates the opportunity either to
        fast-track their professional marketing management qualification, or to embark on a career in business,
        secure in the knowledge that their specialist skills in marketing management.
        This course provides key insights into marketing practice and theory in a range of managerial contexts.
        The focus is on the planning and decision-making processes that are essential to good marketing management.
        The course is designed to cover the core knowledge and skills needed by the modern, professional marketer,
        together with a range of options to allow specialist interests to be pursued.

        \n\n Course aims to:

        \n\t &#8226; Become increasingly independent in their learning style, thereby enhancing their life-long learning skills and employability.
        \n\t &#8226; Gain a deep understanding of marketing, its management and the changing marketing environment.
        \n\t &#8226; Be able to contribute effectively in a range of marketing operational and/or strategic contexts on completion of the programme and to target careers in the profession of marketing.
        \n\t &#8226; Develop both the knowledge and the ability to use a range of marketing practitioner and research techniques.
        \n\t &#8226; Develop a number of key intellectual and transferable skills.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail8">
        &lt;Awarded by University of Gloucestershire&gt;

        \n\n This degree course provides a route to complete an honours degree in one year in business related discipline.
        Successful completion of the degree programme would certainly help students to propel their career forward,
        typically into management roles, or to develop more advanced skills through further study.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail9">
        &lt;Awarded by The University of Northampton&gt;

        \n\n This tourism degree programme has been specifically designed to meet the needs of industry.
        Students are encouraged to take a critical and analytical perspective to their understanding of tourism business theory
        combined with a proactive business development approach throughout.

        \n\n The aims of the award are to develop in learners:

        \n\t &#8226; A broad knowledge of the environment within which tourism businesses operate, whilst developing a sound understanding of the academic foundations which underpin key industry disciplines.
        \n\t &#8226; Knowledge and transferable skills in order that they may present themselves as marketable, well-educated and competent individuals, who are able to succeed in a wide range of tourism career opportunities.
        \n\t &#8226; Relevant skills in order that they may have the ability to manage complex situations professionally.
        \n\t &#8226; Knowledge and intellectual ability that they may confidently express themselves and seek to become lifelong learners
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail10">
        TMC’s Higher Diploma in Hospitality and Tourism Management has been specifically designed to develop the skills and knowledge required to be a competent
        and effective manager in this exciting industry.

        \n\n**Industrial Attachment (IA)
        \n Paid internship; if the IA cannot be completed due to unsuccessful placement, students will study two additional modules as below:

        \n\t &#8226; Hospitality Operations Management
        \n\t &#8226; Communication Management in the Hospitality Industry
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail11">
        This course has NO Industrial Attachment. Students need to complete 16 modules or 12 modules for Advanced Standing before they can graduate from the course.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail12">
        The aim of the International Diploma in Hospitality course is to provide students with the basic knowledge in hospitality.
        This course also provides students with the necessary foundation for undergraduate studies in hospitality,
        while providing students with career opportunities in the leisure, hospitality and tourism sectors.

        \n\n Course modules:

        \n\t &#8226; Principles of Business Communication
        \n\t &#8226; Principles and Practice of Facilities Management
        \n\t &#8226; Principles and Practice of Beverage Services
        \n\t &#8226; Information Communication Technology

        \n\n Course assessment:
        \n Assessment of the modules includes examinations, assignments, projects, presentations, class tests, and/or practical tests

        \n\n Teaching and learning:
        \n There will be a combination of guided studies, lectures, tutorials, seminars, presentations, projects, and computer laboratories sessions.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail13">
        &lt;Awarded by University of Greenwich&gt;

        \n\n This degree is designed as a tailor-made ‘top-up’ programme for holders of relevant Diploma and Higher Diploma qualifications from
        the School of Computing &amp; Mathematical Sciences (CMS). The degree provides students with an up-to-date approach to the recent development
        in computing and current market trends.
        \n\n It helps students understand the requirements for web based applications, allowing students to develop skills such as analysis and modeling techniques. It develops a better understanding of hardware and software capabilities and problem-solving approaches to software development.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail14">
        The Higher Diploma in Infocomm Technology (HDICT) provides students with the necessary theoretical knowledge and practical skills to
        meet excellent career opportunities in the Infocomm Technology (ICT) industry.
        It aims to develop and produce graduates who are well-versed in the critical disciplines required in the field of computing and IT.
        They will possess the necessary personal qualities and technical skills to excel as IT professionals.

        \n\n The course aims to achieve an international standard of high quality training which will lead to a universally recognised qualification,
        enabling graduates to pursue undergraduate programmes at top universities.

        \n\n The objectives of the Higher Diploma in Infocomm Technology are to:

        \n\t &#8226; design and implement high quality and robust software products
        \n\t &#8226; professionally analyse and design information systems
        \n\t &#8226; understand, evaluate, propose and implement computerised solutions to meet varied levels of user requirements
        \n\t &#8226; demonstrate effective inter-personal skills when working in groups or leading teams
        \n\t &#8226; professionally communicate and present proposals, findings and results
        \n\t &#8226; pursue higher level studies at universities
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail15">
        The aim of the International Diploma in Information Technology course is to provide students with the basic knowledge in information technology.
        This course also provides students with the necessary foundation for undergraduate studies in information technology,
        while providing students with career opportunities in the IT/IS area in financial, manufacturing and commercial sectors.

        \n\n Course modules:
        \n\t &#8226; Principles of Business Communication
        \n\t &#8226; Basic Computer Principles
        \n\t &#8226; Java Programming
        \n\t &#8226; Information Communication Technology

        \n\n Course assessment:
        \n Assessment of the modules includes examinations, assignments, projects, presentations, class tests, and/or practical tests

        \n\n Teaching and learning:
        \n There will be a combination of guided studies, lectures, tutorials, seminars, presentations, projects, and computer laboratories sessions.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail16">
        The Higher Diploma in Mass Communications provides students with the necessary theoretical knowledge and practical skills
        in the interdisciplinary fields of mass communications, i.e. journalism, film, and multimedia.
        It equips students with general transferable skills which are of relevance to a wide range of careers in the field of mass communications.
        The Higher Diploma is designed to help develop students’ analytical techniques and problem solving skills, enabling them to evaluate evidence,
        arguments and assumptions in the field of mass communications.
    </string>
    <string name="course_detail17">
        The aim of the International Diploma in Mass Communication course is to provide students with the basic knowledge in Mass Communication.
        This course also provides students with the necessary foundation for undergraduate studies in mass communications,
        while providing students with career opportunities in the film, journalism &amp; media sectors.

        \n\n Course modules:
        \n\t &#8226; Principles of Business Communication
        \n\t &#8226; Principles of Mass Communication
        \n\t &#8226; Principles of the Media
        \n\t &#8226; Information Communication Technology

        \n\n Course assessment:
        \n Assessment of the modules includes examinations, assignments, projects, presentations, class tests, and/or practical tests

        \n\n Teaching and learning:
        \n There will be a combination of guided studies, lectures, tutorials, seminars, presentations, projects, and computer laboratories sessions
    </string>

    <string name="course_detail18">
        This psychology with counselling degree enables critical understanding and analysis of human behaviour, thought and emotions.
        Students will Learn scientific skills that are transferable to careers outside Psychology. This is a one year programme which offers learners the opportunity to:

        \n\t &#8226; Provide a critical understanding of psychological data relating to human behavior and experience.
        \n\t &#8226; Equip students with the highly desirable skills and knowledge for employability or to provide the foundations for further study towards a career in counselling psychology or related professions.
        \n\t &#8226; Develop generic and subject specific skills for example; analytic, interpersonal and research skills that are relevant to a range of careers.
        \n\t &#8226; Foster a desire for life-long learning.

        \n\n Students are able to apply to the British Psychological Society for individual membership on graduation from this course.
    </string>

    <string name="course_detail19">
        &lt;Awarded by The University of Northampton&gt;

        \n\n This psychology degree enables critical understanding and analysis of human behaviour, thought and emotions.
        Students will learn scientific skills that are transferable to careers outside Psychology. The course tackle psychological issues in work, education,
        physical and mental health, crime, etc. This is a one year programme which offers learners the opportunity to:

        \n\t &#8226; Provide a critical understanding of psychological data relating to human behaviour and experience.
        \n\t &#8226; Develop generic and subject specific skills for example; analytic, interpersonal and research skills that are relevant to a range of careers.
        \n\t &#8226; Foster a desire for life-long learning.
        \n\n **Students are able to apply to the British Psychological Society for individual membership on graduation from this course.
    </string>

    <string name="course_detail20">
        &lt;Awarded by TMC Academy&gt;

        \n\n The Graduate Diploma of Psychology is suitable for those who wish to study psychology from a CPE-accredited institution
        after having completed an undergraduate degree in another discipline. The Graduate Diploma of Psychology syllabus covers developmental,
        biological, cognitive, social, and abnormal psychology, as well as research design and analysis, and personality and psychological testing.
        This course of study therefore provides students with a comprehensive theoretical background and relevant helping skills to understand mental processes
        and human behaviour.
    </string>

    <string name="course_detail21">
        Psychology is a science which answers questions about human and animal behavior and cognition.
        The Higher Diploma in Psychology with Counselling provides students with a comprehensive theoretical background and research skills
        relevant to studying mental processes and human behaviour. The programme covers a broad range of empirical and practical areas of psychology
        and offers the students an opportunity to begin the development of basic counselling skills.

        \n\n Singapore Psychological Society has agreed that students studying for Higher Diploma in Psychology with Counselling
        at TMC Academy can become members of the Society.  TMC Academy and SPS signed a memorandum of understanding at
        the Singapore Psychological Society Annual General Meeting on Saturday 28th March 2015 to formally recognise the agreement.
        SPS was represented by President Ms Clare Yeo and TMC Academy was represented by Dr Chin Kon Yuen, Executive Chairman.
        Dr Chin said, “I am absolutely delighted to sign this agreement with Singapore Psychological Society
        and I look forward to many of our Higher Diploma in Psychology with Counselling and many of our Psychology degree students becoming members of the SPS.
        More people are choosing to study Psychology in Singapore and at TMC we look forward to growing the membership of SPS
        through all our Psychology diploma courses and Psychology degrees.”
    </string>

    <string name="course_link0">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/diploma-in-accounting-and-finance/</string>
    <string name="course_link1">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-science-honours-in-accounting-and-finance/</string>
    <string name="course_link2">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-science-honours-international-accounting-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link3">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/post-graduate-diploma-in-accounting-a-preparatory-course-for-umkc-master-of-science-in-accounting-msa/</string>
    <string name="course_link4">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/post-graduate-diploma-in-finance-a-preparatory-course-for-umkc-master-of-science-in-finance-msf/</string>
    <string name="course_link5">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-arts-honours-in-accounting-and-financial-management-studies-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link6">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-arts-honours-business-and-management-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link7">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-arts-honours-marketing-management-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link8">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/z-bachelor-of-arts-honours-in-business-management-and-strategy-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link9">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-arts-honours-international-tourism-management-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link10">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/higher-diploma-in-hospitality-and-tourism-management/</string>
    <string name="course_link11">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/higher-diploma-in-tourism-hospitality-and-leisure-management/</string>
    <string name="course_link12">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/international-diploma-in-hospitality/</string>
    <string name="course_link13">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-science-honours-computing-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link14">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/higher-diploma-in-infocomm-technology/</string>
    <string name="course_link15">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/international-diploma-in-information-technology/</string>
    <string name="course_link16">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/higher-diploma-in-mass-communication/</string>
    <string name="course_link17">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/international-diploma-in-mass-communication/</string>
    <string name="course_link18">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-science-honours-psychology-with-counselling-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link19">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/bachelor-of-science-honours-psychology-top-up/</string>
    <string name="course_link20">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/graduate-diploma-of-psychology/</string>
    <string name="course_link21">http://www.tmc.edu.sg/course/higher-diploma-in-psychology-with-counselling/</string>
</resources>
